buckeyeplanet.com 2007-06-07

# BuckeyePlanet - Ohio State Fan Community - Privacy Policy

**Information Collection & Use**  
_Registration_  
In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password. During registration you are required to provide basic contact information (such as email address). We use this information to contact you in the event of a lost password, relay information and/or news in which you have expressed interest, and to verify the validity of new registrations.

You have the option to provide optional supplementary information (such as location and birthdate) to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site, and so that our userbase can enjoy a community atmosphere knowing more about one another.

Bryants.net is the sole owner of the information collected on BuckeyePlanet. Bryants.net collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site. This allows you to maintain a login between visits, enjoy access to areas restricted to registered users, and provides us a means of tracking usage patterns so that we know what's working, and what's not.

**Surveys or Contests**  
From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes.

_Tell-A-Friend_  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, or content therein, we will ask you for your friendâ€™s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Bryants.net does not store this information.

_Uses of Information_  
BuckeyePlanet uses the information collected from you to better understand the demographics, interests and behavior of our collective audience. We do not share individual information about you with third-parties in the process.

**Communications from the Site**  
_Service-related Announcements_  
We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is going to be suspended for maintenance for an unusual period, we might send you an email. 

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. However, these communications will be uncommon.

_Customer Service_  
Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account.

_Profile_  
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, to create a â€œprofileâ€ of your preferences. We do not tie your personally identifiable information to information in the profile.

We do not share your profile with other third parties.

_Personally identifiable information:_  
We DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties.

_Legal Disclaimer_  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

_Log Files_  
As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track usersâ€™ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

_Cookies_  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a userâ€™s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browserâ€™s â€œhelpâ€ file.

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you donâ€™t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as the arcade, will be limited.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by this site only.

_Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)_  
We may employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a userâ€™s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customersâ€™ personally identifiable information. 

We may use clear gifs in future HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications. If we find a time and reason to send emails such as this out in the future you would have to opt-in to receive them, and would be able to opt-out at any time. Examples of how this might be put to use is an email subscription service where boxscores are sent each Saturday following games. 

_Links to Other Sites_  
This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Bryants.net/BuckeyePlanet. Please be aware that we, Bryants.net/BuckeyePlanet, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

_Bulletin Boards/Chat Rooms_  
If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information that you submit (for example, posting your email address in a thread, or other personal and/or contact info) there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information _you choose to submit_ in these forums. 

_'Private Messages/Private Messaging'_  
This site offers an in-house means of communication called 'Private Messaging'. The administrator of the site reserve the right to read and/or monitor these messages. We consider this an extreme and distasteful measure, and would prefer to avoid it at all costs. When it hits our databases, to the time that it is removed by you, we are obligated to protect ourselves from our resources being used for illegal or undesireable purposes. We take privacy very seriously, and can only imagine extreme conditions and circumstances leading to such a step. We cannot read PMs that you have deleted from your folders. If you require an off-site means of communication, use email.

_Access to Personally Identifiable Information_  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information (UserCP) page.

_Security_  
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

_Business Transitions_  
In the unlikely event BuckeyePlanet goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email and/or prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information during which time you may choose to edit, delete or suspend your account.

_Changes in this Privacy Statement_  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

_Contact Us_  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us [here](http://www.buckeyeplanet.com/forum/sendmessage.php).
